9th ji, I just welcome you, hello, machine like, tell me where is the attention and trend wicket, I am on the first day, so I
think that writing actress is on the
table, if not today then tomorrow we will cross 15909
and comment, it means extremely good
pick up the data, macro data is gold,
corporate results, you have seen it from
bank HDFC Bank, welcome to the
best profit saver on the 17382 and today I will give you it's
large cap, so in the last step,
now I will just do it
in Reliance HDFC Bank, today I will give
you news that Maruti has deepened 18,000
crores in the next five years and will invest
10 lakh vehicles and he himself in laughter Vijay
on you, two sitting multiple, send food to homes,
overhead tank fiber multiple,
Maruti is a weapon running plant, so
my first pick is unquestionably Maruti 73,
take ₹100, Vacancy Vision, if you want to
sell them in the next year, then you can imagine
Vision 7373, take 10
Maruti from Swapna Dosh 2198, second brother  He is
very bullish on record to
sanctions go to record, Seit & General
Insurance World Mobile at 1540 42,
take stopped for 1505 target of
more than 60, give a plate, if it does not move today,
but in the second, your midcap banks will definitely move,
you just do it, you are already seeing a change in Bandhan Bank, Aryan and
IDFC First One Max,
you have a target of 14 15 to 11 325,
it will go to 345 in the month of July,
Bandhan, RBL Bank, IDFC, year and 22
midcap IT will be the best performer in the SE
Internship TDS, let's see a
good momentum coming in front of you in winters, he
can see, thank you very much Wasim sir, it is a
good moment in Maruti, ICICI
Lombard and in the form of SWIFT, you are
seeing trends on Bandhan Bank, RBL Bank and IDBI and IDFC First Bank, sir